{
    "subject": "resource/A_Buffalope's_Tale",
    "predicate": "ontology/author",
    "object": "resource/Philip_Caveney",
    "human_readable": "A Buffalope's Tale was written by Philip Caveney.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9557099938392639,
            "question": "Who wrote the book 'A Buffalope's Tale'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8803539872169495,
            "question": "Is 'A Buffalope's Tale' a novel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7462118268013,
            "question": "Can you name a book written by Philip Caveney?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.660533607006073,
            "question": "Is there a particular theme explored in 'A Buffalope's Tale'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6552399396896362,
            "question": "What is the title of Philip Caveney's book?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6220927834510803,
            "question": "What kind of story might 'A Buffalope's Tale' tell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6120739579200745,
            "question": "What could the title 'A Buffalope's Tale' suggest about the book?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5711675882339478,
            "question": "Where might one find more information about 'A Buffalope's Tale'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45484036207199097,
            "question": "What genre might 'A Buffalope's Tale' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3536527752876282,
            "question": "Do you know any other works by Philip Caveney?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=A Buffalope's Tale was written by Philip Caveney.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2130_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might 'A Buffalope's Tale' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2130_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might one find more information about 'A Buffalope's Tale'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2130_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What could the title 'A Buffalope's Tale' suggest about the book?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2130_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2130_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2130_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2130_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2130_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2130_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2130_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2130_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2130_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2130_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2130_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that A Buffalope's Tale is indeed a book written by Philip Caveney."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"A Buffalope's Tale\" is authored by Philip Caveney, which directly supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}